

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Abzal Suan











PROFILE

I have a results-focused attitude to creating SPA, using React(JS/TS), Redux.

I have a sufficient experience in React development from small pet projects to large architectural and testable web applications.

My most important skills are problem solving, proactivity and total contribution.

Ready to consider project work and fulltime employment.

CONTACTS



abzal008suan@gmail.com



+7 952 460 9665



Sberclass outsource team | 2021 august - present

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Creating interactive lessons using React, Hooks, emotionJS
- Engaged in refactoring, bug fixing.
- Reusable components development
- StoryBook components

Freelance | 2021 March - 2021 august

- Work with and migrating to Hooks, TypeScript
- Engaged in refactoring, bug fixing.
- Reusable components development
- Unit Testing and StoryBook components

Insen group(beauty and wellness) | Senior manufacturing master | 2020 Apr - 2021 Feb

- Management of the manufacturing area.
- Increasing the efficiency of the team
- Product and service quality monitoring
- Development of new and improvement of existing technological processes and modes

DanceFile | Photographer | 2017 Oct - 2020 Feb

- Shooting and filming in various conditions
- Equipment service
- Selection of the necessary photographic equipment
- Processing, design, printing of images

SKILLS

- REACT / REDUX (toolkit) / MIDDLEWARE
- JAVASCRIPT / TYPESCRIPT
- AXIOS / RESTAPI
- NODE.JS / EXPRESS / MONGODB
- MATERIAL-UI / ANT-DESIGN
- HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS / EMOTION JS
- UNIT TESTS / STORYBOOK
- GIT/GITLAB
- English Upper-Intermediate in progress

EDUCATION

2021 March

IT-INCUBATOR

2017 - 2022

Moscow Polytechnic University Electrical engineering (EXTRAMURAL)

2014 - 2017

Almaty College of Transport and Technology Auto electrician





Абзал Суан











обо мне

Я Front-end разработчик, который ориентирован на результат при создании SPA с использованием React (JS/TS), Redux.

У меня достаточный опыт в React разработке, начиная от маленьких пет проектов, до больших архитектурных и тестируемых web-приложении.

Мои самые главные навыки это умение решать проблемы, проактивность и полный вклад.

Готов рассмотреть предложения о

КОНТАКТЫ



abzal008suan@gmail.com



+7 952 460 9665



Москва, Россия

НАВЫКИ

- REACT / REDUX (toolkit) / MIDDI FWARE
- JAVASCRIPT/TYPESCRIPT
- AXIOS / RESTAPI
- NODE.JS/EXPRESS/MONGODB
- MATERIAL-UI / ANT-DESIGN
- HTML5/CSS3/SASS/EMOTION JS
- UNIT TESTS / STORYBOOK
- GIT/GITLAB
- progress

ОПЫТ РАБОТЫ

Сберкласс outsource команда I август 2021 — по настоящее время

- разработка интерактивных приложении с использованием React, Hookc, emotionJS
- разработка reusable компонентов
- написание модульных StoryBook документации
- был вовлечен в refactoring и bug fixing

Фриланс I Март 2021 — август 2021

- разработка React приложении с использованием redux, react-redux, react-router-dom, redux middleware
- переход и работа с TypeScript и Hooks
- был вовлечен в refactoring и bug fixing

Инсен групп | Старший мастер | Апр 2020 — фев 2021

- руководство производственным участком.
- повышение эффективности команды
- разработка новых и совершенствование действующих

DanceFile | Фотограф/оператор| Окт 2017 — фев 2020

- непосредственный процесс съёмки
- осуществление съемок в различных условиях
- обслуживание оборудования
- подбор необходимой фототехники и атрибутики
- обработка, оформление, печать снимков

ОБРАЗОВАНИЕ

Март 2021

IT-INCUBATOR

Front-end разработчик (React/Redux/TypeScript)

2017 - 2022

Московский политехнический университет электроэнергетика и электротехника (заочно)

2014 - 2017

АКПТиТ

Автоэлектрик